webpackJsonp([78],{"./app/desktop/containers/HomePage/constants.js":function(e,o,n){"use strict";n.d(o,"l",function(){return t}),n.d(o,"m",function(){return i}),n.d(o,"n",function(){return a}),n.d(o,"o",function(){return s}),n.d(o,"b",function(){return r}),n.d(o,"c",function(){return c}),n.d(o,"d",function(){return u}),n.d(o,"e",function(){return d}),n.d(o,"f",function(){return l}),n.d(o,"h",function(){return h}),n.d(o,"g",function(){return f}),n.d(o,"i",function(){return p}),n.d(o,"j",function(){return y}),n.d(o,"k",function(){return m}),n.d(o,"a",function(){return b});var t="LOAD_HOMEPAGE_CONFIG",i="LOAD_HOMEPAGE_CONFIG_SUCCESS",a="GET_HOMEPAGE_CAROUSEL_PRODUCTS",s="GET_HOMEPAGE_CAROUSEL_PRODUCTS_SUCCESS",r="banners",c="testimonials",u="popularCategories",d="collectionCarouselAndOtherBanners",l="howZefoDoIt",h="trippleBannerWithHeading",f="iconHeader",p="specialOffers",y="processVideo",m="aboutZefo",b="productCarousal"},"./app/desktop/containers/HomePage/reducer.js":function(e,o,n){"use strict";function t(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:c,o=arguments[1];switch(o.type){case a.m:return e.set("bodyConfig",n.i(i.fromJS)(o.body.bodyConfig)).set("productList",n.i(i.fromJS)({}));case a.o:return e.set("productList",n.i(i.fromJS)(o.body));case s.i:return u(e,o.productID,!0,o.params);case s.j:return u(e,o.productID,!1,o.params);case s.l:return u(e,o.productID,o.revertTo,o.params);default:return e}}Object.defineProperty(o,"__esModule",{value:!0});var i=n("./node_modules/immutable/dist/immutable.js"),a=(n.n(i),n("./app/desktop/containers/HomePage/constants.js")),s=n("./app/desktop/containers/App/constants.js"),r=n("./app/helpers/product.js");n.d(o,"moveProductToWishlist",function(){return u});var c=n.i(i.fromJS)({bodyConfig:[],productList:{}}),u=function(e,o,t,i){var a=void 0;if(i&&i.tag&&(a=n.i(r.b)(e.getIn(["productList",i.tag]),o)),a>-1){var s=e.getIn(["productList",i.tag,a]);return e.setIn(["productList",i.tag,a],n.i(r.c)(s,t))}return e};o.default=t},"./app/helpers/product.js":function(e,o,n){"use strict";var t=n("./app/global-constants.js"),i=n("./app/services/config/conditionConfig.js"),a=n("./app/services/config/buyBackConfig.js"),s=n("./node_modules/immutable/dist/immutable.js");n.n(s),n.d(o,"a",function(){return r}),n.d(o,"e",function(){return c}),n.d(o,"d",function(){return u}),n.d(o,"b",function(){return d}),n.d(o,"c",function(){return l}),n.d(o,"g",function(){return h}),n.d(o,"f",function(){return f}),n.d(o,"h",function(){return p}),n.d(o,"i",function(){return y});var r=function(e,o){var n=e.get("slugName");return"/"+o+"/product/"+(n&&n.toLowerCase()||e.get("id"))},c=function(e){return parseInt(e.get("offerPrice")||e.get("price"),10)},u=function(e,o){return e.get("stockSize")>t.b?o>=t.b:o>e.get("stockSize")},d=function(e,o){return e&&e.findIndex(function(e){return e.get("id")===o})},l=function(e,o){return e.set("isOnWishList",!!o)},h=function(e){var o=e.get("categoryType"),t=e.get("subCategoryType"),a=e.get("condition");return-1!==i.a.indexOf(o)?n.i(i.b)(i.c[o])[a&&a.toLowerCase()]:-1!==i.d.indexOf(o)?n.i(i.e)("TVs")[a&&a.toLowerCase()]:-1!==i.f.indexOf(o)?n.i(i.g)()[a&&a.toLowerCase()]:n.i(i.h)(t)[a&&a.toLowerCase()]},f=function(e){var o=i.c[e]?i.c[e]:e,t=void 0;return i.f.indexOf(e)>-1?t=n.i(i.g)():i.d.indexOf(e)>-1?t=n.i(i.e)("TVs"):i.a.indexOf(e)>-1?t=n.i(i.b)(o):i.i.indexOf(e)>-1?t=n.i(i.h)(o):i.j.indexOf(e)>-1&&(t=n.i(i.k)(o)),t},p=function(e){return i.i.indexOf(e)>-1||i.j.indexOf(e)>-1?a.a:a.b[e]?a.b[e]:n.i(s.fromJS)([])},y=function(e){return!("mobile"===e.get("categoryType")||"kids"===e.get("categoryType")||"air-conditioner"===e.get("categoryType")||"lamps"===String(e.get("categoryType")).toLowerCase()||"Office Chairs"===e.get("subCategoryType")||"Study Tables"===e.get("subCategoryType"))}},"./app/services/config/buyBackConfig.js":function(e,o,n){"use strict";var t=n("./node_modules/immutable/dist/immutable.js");n.n(t),n.d(o,"a",function(){return i}),n.d(o,"b",function(){return a});var i=n.i(t.fromJS)([{question:"What is Zefo buyback policy?",answers:["Zefo buyback policy is a re-sale assurance provided by Zefo where in Zefo will guarantee a re-sale of your furniture at a pre-defined price. This is policy is applicable on selected furniture which display the buyback logo/sign on the Zefo website."]},{question:"How long is the re-sale assurance valid for?",answers:["This buyback policy is applicable on all furniture which have a buyback logo/sign on the website."]},{question:"How much money do I get?",answers:["For furniture within 6 months of date of delivery, Zefo will help you find a buyer at 70% of the invoice price paid for the furniture. For furniture within 6-12 months of date of delivery, Zefo will help find a buyer for 60% of the invoice price paid for the product."]},{question:"How do I re-sell eligible product(s)?",answers:["You can reach out to us across various communication channels to initiate buyback for your product: e-mail at : contact@gozefo.com and mention product name and order confirmation number.Call/whatsapp on  +91 9066 020 755 and advise the Zefo representative that you wish to avail the buyback offer. Post this, a Zefo representative will reach out to you to assess the product for any damages and schedule a convenient pick-up. At the time of pick-up, Zefo will pay the re-sale guarantee amount as an upfront security deposit, which will be non-refundable in case we are unable to find a buyer for your furniture."]},{question:"What items are not accepted for buyback?",answers:["Breakages caused by impacts or accidents.","Any damages to the product that has been stored, assembled or installed incorrectly, used inappropriately, abused, misused, altered, accidentally damaged, or cleaned using the wrong cleaning methods or cleaning products.","Broken glass items like table tops, cabinet glass doors, mirrors.","If any parts of the furniture are broken and coming apart like a sofa/table/chair legs.","Sofas with damaged springs.","Damaged mechanism for hydraulic storage / sofa beds, etc.","There should be no missing parts in the furniture sets, e.g. a chair missing/broken in a dining table set or handles / locks / keys missing in a wardrobe.","Furniture with bed-bugs / termites, etc.","Furniture having incomplete hardware due to which the product can’t be reassembled.","Any major tears / non-removable stains on upholstery","Furniture that have been modified since purchase (e.g., re-painting, re-upholstering, addition of new parts, etc.)","Any other structural damages which makes the Furniture unusable in as-is condition."]},{question:"How long does the entire process take?",answers:["After your buyback request is received, a Zefo representative will get in touch with you within 48 working hours. Post confirmation, Zefo will pick up the furniture within 72 hours."]},{question:"What if it’s been over 12 months from date of delivery? Would Zefo still help find a buyer for the furniture?",answers:["Yes! Zefo will help you in finding a buyer for your furniture after 12 months too. However, we cannot provide a price guarantee for that furniture as of now."]},{question:"What Furniture is it valid on?",answers:["This buyback policy is applicable on all furniture which have a buyback pin/logo on the website."]},{question:"Who do I contact for help?",answers:["Email Zefo at contact@gozefo.com or call/whatsapp on  +91 9066 020 755."]}]),a={mobile:n.i(t.fromJS)([{question:"What is Buyback?",answers:["Zefo buyback policy is a re-sale assurance provided by Zefo where in Zefo will guarantee a re-sale of your Mobile phone at a pre-defined price. This policy is applicable on selected mobile phones which display the buyback logo/sign on the Zefo website."]},{question:"How it Works?",answers:["If you wish to avail buyback facility please call/whatsapp us on +91 9066 020 755 or email us at contact@gozefo.com, Once your buyback request is received, a Zefo representative will get in touch with you within 48 working hours. Post confirmation, Zefo will pick up the mobile phone within 72 hours and pay you cash up front. Invoice is mandatory to avail buyback offer."]},{question:"ITEMS NOT ACCEPTED FOR BUYBACK",answers:["Breakages caused by impacts or accidents.","Any damages to the product that has been stored incorrectly, used inappropriately, abused, misused, altered, accidentally damaged, or cleaned using the wrong cleaning methods or cleaning products.","Broken screen cases or screen misalignment caused due to negligence in usage","If any parts of the mobile phone are broken or missing as per the sales package mentioned while purchase of the product.","Damaged mechanism for functioning of buttons of the mobile phone.","Non-removable stains on body of the mobile phone","Mobile phones that have been modified since purchase (e.g. addition of new parts, damaged or scratched screen protectors etc.)","Any other damages which makes the mobile phones unusable in as-is condition."]},{question:"IS BUYBACK AVAILABLE IF IT'S BEEN OVER 12 MONTHS FROM THE DATE OF DELIVERY?",answers:["Zefo will help you in finding a buyer for your mobile phone after 12 months too. However, we cannot provide a price guarantee for that mobile phone as of now"]},{question:"WHO DO I CONTACT FOR HELP?",answers:["Email Zefo at contact@gozefo.com or call/whatsapp on +91 9066 020 755."]}]),"washing-machine":n.i(t.fromJS)([{question:"What is Buyback?",answers:["Zefo buyback policy is a re-sale assurance provided by Zefo where in Zefo will guarantee a re-sale of your Washing Machine at a pre-defined price. This policy is applicable on selected Washing Machines which display the buyback logo/sign on the Zefo website."]},{question:"How it Works?",answers:["If you wish to avail buyback facility for Washing Machines, please call/whatsapp us on +91 9066 020 755 or email us at contact@gozefo.com. After your buyback request is received, a Zefo representative will get in touch with you within 48 working hours. Post inspection, Zefo will pick up the Washing Machine within 72 hours and pay you cash upfront. Invoice is mandatory to avail buyback offer."]},{question:"ITEMS NOT ACCEPTED FOR BUYBACK",answers:["Breakages caused by impacts or accidents.","Any damages to the product that has been stored incorrectly, used inappropriately, abused, misused, altered, accidentally damaged, or cleaned using the wrong cleaning methods or cleaning products.","There should be no missing parts in the Washing Machine, e.g. power cord, inlet pipe, outlet pipe, lid, etc.","Washing Machines that have been modified since purchase (e.g. addition of new parts, replacement of original parts, other physical modifications etc.)","Any other damages which makes the Washing Machine unusable in as-is condition."]},{question:"IS BUYBACK AVAILABLE IF IT'S BEEN OVER 12 MONTHS FROM THE DATE OF DELIVERY?",answers:["Zefo will help you in finding a buyer for your Washing Machine after 12 months too. However, we cannot provide a price guarantee for that Washing Machine as of now"]},{question:"WHO DO I CONTACT FOR HELP?",answers:["Email Zefo at contact@gozefo.com or call/whatsapp on +91 9066 020 755."]}]),refrigerators:n.i(t.fromJS)([{question:"What is Buyback?",answers:["Zefo buyback policy is a re-sale assurance provided by Zefo where in Zefo will guarantee a re-sale of your Refrigerator at a pre-defined price. This policy is applicable on selected Refrigerators which display the buyback logo/sign on the Zefo website."]},{question:"How it Works?",answers:["If you wish to avail buyback facility for Refrigerators, please call/whatsapp us on +91 9066 020 755 or email us at contact@gozefo.com. After your buyback request is received, a Zefo representative will get in touch with you within 48 working hours. Post inspection, Zefo will pick up the Refrigerator within 72 hours and pay you cash upfront. Invoice is mandatory to avail buyback offer."]},{question:"ITEMS NOT ACCEPTED FOR BUYBACK",answers:["Breakages caused by impacts or accidents.","Any damages to the product that has been stored incorrectly, used inappropriately, abused, misused, altered, accidentally damaged, or cleaned using the wrong cleaning methods or cleaning products.","There should be no missing parts in the Refrigerator, e.g. ice tray, bottle guard, vegetable box, shelves etc.","Refrigerators that have been modified since purchase (e.g. addition of new parts, replacement of original parts, other physical modifications etc.)","Any other damages which makes the Refrigerator unusable in as-is condition."]},{question:"IS BUYBACK AVAILABLE IF IT'S BEEN OVER 12 MONTHS FROM THE DATE OF DELIVERY?",answers:["Zefo will help you in finding a buyer for your Refrigerator after 12 months too. However, we cannot provide a price guarantee for that Refrigerator as of now"]},{question:"WHO DO I CONTACT FOR HELP?",answers:["Email Zefo at contact@gozefo.com or call/whatsapp on +91 9066 020 755."]}]),"air-conditioner":n.i(t.fromJS)([{question:"What is Buyback?",answers:["Zefo buyback policy is a re-sale assurance provided by Zefo where in Zefo will guarantee a re-sale of your AC at a pre-defined price. This policy is applicable on selected ACs which display the buyback logo/sign on the Zefo website."]},{question:"How it Works?",answers:["If you wish to avail buyback facility for ACs, please call/whatsapp us on +91 9066 020 755 or email us at contact@gozefo.com. After your buyback request is received, a Zefo representative will get in touch with you within 48 working hours. Post inspection, Zefo will pick up the AC within 72 hours and pay you cash upfront. Invoice is mandatory to avail buyback offer."]},{question:"ITEMS NOT ACCEPTED FOR BUYBACK",answers:["Breakages caused by impacts or accidents.","Any damages to the product that has been stored, assembled or installed incorrectly, used inappropriately, abused, misused, altered, accidentally damaged, or cleaned using the wrong cleaning methods or cleaning products.","There should be no missing parts in the AC, e.g. remote, indoor stand, outdoor stand, copper wire, etc.","ACs that have been modified since purchase (e.g. addition of new parts, replacement of original parts, other physical modifications etc.)","Any other damages which makes the AC unusable in as-is condition."]},{question:"IS BUYBACK AVAILABLE IF IT'S BEEN OVER 12 MONTHS FROM THE DATE OF DELIVERY?",answers:["Zefo will help you in finding a buyer for your AC after 12 months too. However, we cannot provide a price guarantee for that AC as of now"]},{question:"WHO DO I CONTACT FOR HELP?",answers:["Email Zefo at contact@gozefo.com or call/whatsapp on +91 9066 020 755."]}]),microwave:n.i(t.fromJS)([{question:"What is Buyback?",answers:["Zefo buyback policy is a re-sale assurance provided by Zefo where in Zefo will guarantee a re-sale of your Microwave at a pre-defined price. This policy is applicable on selected Microwaves which display the buyback logo/sign on the Zefo website."]},{question:"How it Works?",answers:["If you wish to avail buyback facility for Microwaves, please call/whatsapp us on +91 9066 020 755 or email us at contact@gozefo.com. After your buyback request is received, a Zefo representative will get in touch with you within 48 working hours. Post inspection, Zefo will pick up the Microwave within 72 hours and pay you cash upfront. Invoice is mandatory to avail buyback offer."]},{question:"ITEMS NOT ACCEPTED FOR BUYBACK",answers:["Breakages caused by impacts or accidents.","Any damages to the product that has been stored, assembled or installed incorrectly, used inappropriately, abused, misused, altered, accidentally damaged, or cleaned using the wrong cleaning methods or cleaning products.","There should be no missing parts in the Microwave, e.g. rotating ring, glass dish, power cord, etc.","Microwaves that have been modified since purchase (e.g. addition of new parts, replacement of original parts, other physical modifications etc.)","Any other damages which makes the Microwave unusable in as-is condition."]},{question:"IS BUYBACK AVAILABLE IF IT'S BEEN OVER 12 MONTHS FROM THE DATE OF DELIVERY?",answers:["Zefo will help you in finding a buyer for your Microwave after 12 months too. However, we cannot provide a price guarantee for that Microwave as of now"]},{question:"WHO DO I CONTACT FOR HELP?",answers:["Email Zefo at contact@gozefo.com or call/whatsapp on +91 9066 020 755."]}]),TV:n.i(t.fromJS)([{question:"What is Buyback?",answers:["Zefo buyback policy is a re-sale assurance provided by Zefo where in Zefo will guarantee a re-sale of your TV at a pre-defined price. This policy is applicable on selected TVs which display the buyback logo/sign on the Zefo website."]},{question:"How it Works?",answers:["If you wish to avail buyback facility for TVs, please call/whatsapp us on +91 9066 020 755 or email us at contact@gozefo.com. After your buyback request is received, a Zefo representative will get in touch with you within 48 working hours. Post inspection, Zefo will pick up the TV within 72 hours and pay you cash upfront. Invoice is mandatory to avail buyback offer."]},{question:"ITEMS NOT ACCEPTED FOR BUYBACK",answers:["Breakages caused by impacts or accidents.","Any damages to the product that has been stored, assembled or installed incorrectly, used inappropriately, abused, misused, altered, accidentally damaged, or cleaned using the wrong cleaning methods or cleaning products.","There should be no missing parts in the TV, e.g. remote, 3D glasses, stand / mount, power cord etc.","TVs that have been modified since purchase (e.g. addition of new parts, replacement of original parts, other physical modifications etc.)","Any other damages which makes the TV unusable in as-is condition."]},{question:"IS BUYBACK AVAILABLE IF IT'S BEEN OVER 12 MONTHS FROM THE DATE OF DELIVERY?",answers:["Zefo will help you in finding a buyer for your TV after 12 months too. However, we cannot provide a price guarantee for that TV as of now"]},{question:"WHO DO I CONTACT FOR HELP?",answers:["Email Zefo at contact@gozefo.com or call/whatsapp on +91 9066 020 755."]}])}},"./app/services/config/conditionConfig.js":function(e,o,n){"use strict";n.d(o,"h",function(){return t}),n.d(o,"k",function(){return i}),n.d(o,"b",function(){return a}),n.d(o,"e",function(){return s}),n.d(o,"g",function(){return r}),n.d(o,"i",function(){return c}),n.d(o,"a",function(){return u}),n.d(o,"d",function(){return d}),n.d(o,"f",function(){return l}),n.d(o,"j",function(){return h}),n.d(o,"c",function(){return f});var t=function(e){return{"unboxed plus":"Unboxed Plus "+e+" are flawless products with no defects. They are typically excess or surplus stocks from manufacturers/retailers.",unboxed:"Unboxed "+e+" are unused. These include Factory Seconds, Surplus Stock, Slow-moving Inventory and Returns for other online retailers. These furniture have minor defects due to which they could not be sold as new (scratches, misalignments etc.) but are otherwise in mint condition.","like new":"Like New "+e+" are in fantastic condition. They show virtually no signs of use and could easily pass off as brand new pieces.","gently used":"Gently Used "+e+" are in great condition overall, but show minor signs of previous use, for example scuff marks, scratches, or some other cosmetic defects.","well used":"Well Used "+e+" are completely functional overall, but show noticeable signs of previous use. Furniture that has multiple tears, stains, cracks, scratches etc would fall into this category.",refurbished:"Refurbished "+e+" have been used, but have since been restored to a fully functional, and nearly perfect aesthetic condition. While some minor defects like scratches / dents may exist on the product, by and large these are in near new condition.","factory seconds plus":"Factory Seconds Plus "+e+" are flawless products with no defects. They are typically excess or surplus stocks from manufacturers/retailers.","factory seconds":"Factory Seconds "+e+" are unused. These include Factory Seconds, Surplus Stock, Slow-moving Inventory and Returns for other online retailers. These furniture have minor defects due to which they could not be sold as new (scratches, misalignments etc.) but are otherwise in mint condition."}},i=function(e){return{unboxed:"Unboxed "+e+" are unused. These include Factory Seconds, Surplus Stock, Slow-moving Inventory and Returns for other online retailers. These furniture have minor defects due to which they could not be sold as new (scratches, misalignments etc.) but are otherwise in mint condition.",refurbished:"Refurbished "+e+" have been used, but have since been restored to a fully functional, and nearly perfect aesthetic condition. While some minor defects like scratches / dents may exist on the product, by and large these are in near new condition.","factory seconds":"Factory Seconds "+e+" are unused. These include Factory Seconds, Surplus Stock, Slow-moving Inventory and Returns for other online retailers. These furniture have minor defects due to which they could not be sold as new (scratches, misalignments etc.) but are otherwise in mint condition."}},a=function(e){return{"unboxed plus":"Unboxed Plus "+e+" are flawless products, and typically excess or surplus stock. These products are in perfect condition.",unboxed:"Unboxed "+e+" are unused or used very temporarily. These include Factory Seconds, Surplus Stock, Display Products at stores and Returns for other e-commerce players. These products are in mint condition with extremely minor damages, if any.","like new":"Like New "+e+" are in fantastic condition. They show minimal sign of usage and could easily pass off as brand new pieces.","gently used":"These "+e+" are in great condition overall, but show minor signs of previous use, for example scuff marks, scratches, or some other cosmetic defects. They have been rigorously tested and are in fully working condition.","well used":"These "+e+" are in fully functional condition, but show noticeable signs of previous use. These appliances often have scuff marks, scratches, rusting or other noticeable cosmetic defects. They have been rigorously tested and in fully working condition, and have typically been used for upwards of 5 years.","factory seconds plus":"Factory Seconds Plus "+e+" are flawless products, and typically excess or surplus stock. These products are in perfect condition.","factory seconds":"Factory Seconds "+e+" are unused or used very temporarily. These include Factory Seconds, Surplus Stock, Display Products at stores and Returns for other e-commerce players. These products are in mint condition with extremely minor damages, if any."}},s=function(e){return{"unboxed plus":"Unboxed Plus "+e+" are flawless products, and typically excess or surplus stock. These products are in perfect condition.",unboxed:"Unboxed "+e+" are unused or used very temporarily. These include Factory Seconds, Surplus Stock, Display Products at stores and Returns for other e-commerce players. These products are in mint condition with extremely minor damages, if any.","like new":"Like New "+e+" are in fantastic condition. They show minimal sign of usage and could easily pass off as brand new TVs.","gently used":"Gently Used "+e+" are in great condition overall, but show minor signs of previous use, for example scuff marks, scratches , possibly defective ports, replaced universal remote etc.","well used":"Well Used "+e+" are completely functional units, but have noticeable signs of previous use. These TVs often have scratches, scuff marks, defective ports, replaced universal remote etc, and have been used for upwards of 3 years.","factory seconds":"Factory Seconds "+e+" are unused or used very temporarily. These include Factory Seconds, Surplus Stock, Display Products at stores and Returns for other e-commerce players. These products are in mint condition with extremely minor damages, if any.","factory seconds plus":"Factory Seconds Plus "+e+" are flawless products, and typically excess or surplus stock. These products are in perfect condition."}},r=function(){return{"unboxed plus":"Unboxed Plus Mobiles are flawless, typically excess or surplus stock. These are in perfect condition.",unboxed:"Unboxed Mobiles include Factory Seconds, Surplus Stock and Returns for other e-commerce players. These products are in mint condition with extremely minor damages, if any.","brand restored":"Brand Restored Mobiles have been restored to their factory-like conditions by the brand manufacturer. These products are in mint condition with extremely minor damages, if any.",restored:"Restored Mobiles have been restored to their factory-like conditions by professional mobile service experts. These products are in mint condition with extremely minor damages, if any.","like new":"Like New Mobiles are in fantastic condition. They show minimal sign of usage (minor scratches etc.) and could easily pass off as brand new Mobiles.","gently used":"Gently Used mobiles are in great condition overall, but show minor signs of previous use. Typically these products have been used for a very brief period of time. They have been rigorously tested and are in fully working condition.","well used":"Well Used mobiles are in fully functional condition, but show noticeable signs of previous use. These products could have minor scratches, dents or other noticeable cosmetic defects. They have been rigorously tested and are in fully working condition.","factory seconds plus":"Factory Seconds Plus Mobiles are flawless, typically excess or surplus stock. These are in perfect condition.","factory seconds":"Factory Seconds Mobiles include Factory Seconds, Surplus Stock and Returns for other e-commerce players. These products are in mint condition with extremely minor damages, if any."}},c=["sofas","beds","tables","chairs","storage","furniture-new","new","deals","kids","dining-tables","office","Mattresses",""],u=["washing-machine","refrigerators","microwave","air-conditioner"],d=["TV"],l=["mobile"],h=["lamps","Lamps"],f={"washing-machine":"Washing Machines","dining-tables":"Dining Tables",refrigerators:"Refrigerators",microwave:"Microwaves","air-conditioner":"Air Conditioner"}}});